https://www.mclaincycle.com/articles/mclain-cycle-privacy-policy-pg1590.htm

Full-Suspension
29-Inch Wheel (29ers)
Kids
12-Inch (2-4 yr. old)
16-Inch (3-6 yr. old)
20-Inch (5-8 yr. old)
24-Inch (7+ yr. old)
Gloves
Jerseys/Tops (Short Sleeve)
Outerwear
Protective/Armor
Running
Jerseys/Tops (Long Sleeve)
Shirts/Tops (Casual)
Shorts/Bottoms
Shorts/Bottoms (Casual)
FINANCING
PRIVACY POLICY Updated: Effective July 1, 2019This Privacy Statement applies to mclaincycle.com owned and operated by McLain Cycle Shop,Inc. ("McLain Cycle Shop", "We", "Us", "Our"). This privacy statement describes how McLain Cycle Shop collects and uses the personal information you provide on the domain umbrella of www.mclaincycle.com, our mobile sites and mobile applications, and any other application or access point we make available to you (collectively, our "Web Properties").If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, please contact us.Collection and Use of Personal InformationWe collect certain personal information that you provide directly to us. For example, we collect the following personal information from you:Contact Information such as your name and email address.If you elect to purchase a product we offer, we ask you to provide billing Information such as billing address, credit card number and phone number.Information We Collect Automatically on Our Web PropertiesAs is true of most websites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system, as well as the other information listed in the Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies section below. We do link this collected data to other information we collect about you.We use the information we collect from you to:Administer your account.Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products.Fulfill your order.Link or combine with other information we receive from third parties to help understand your needs, provide you with better service and for marketing purposes.Monitor and analyze activity on our Web Properties.Provide, improve, maintain and operate our services.Respond to customer service requests and provide support.Respond to your comments, concerns and questions.Share your email address with your organization upon request. If the email address under which you have registered your account belongs to or is controlled by an organization (with the exception of known ISP email providers such as Gmail, Hotmail, etc.), we may disclose that email address to that organization in order to help it understand who is using McLain Cycle Shop.We are based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using our products or Web Properties or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S.Choice/Opt-Out for Communications from UsCustomers can opt out of being contacted by us by following the opt-out instructions located in the emails we may send you, by changing your privacy settings in the Service, or by contacting us at any time.However, McLain Cycle Shop reserves the right to send its existing customers certain communications relating to the Service as part of our commercial relationship with you, such as service announcements and administrative messages, without offering the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.Information SharingExcept as provided for in our User Agreement (or other subscription agreement you entered into with us, if any) and this Policy, we do not disclose your personal information to third parties without your consent.We do not sell any of your personal information to third parties or allow third parties to use it for their marketing purposes. McLain Cycle Shop uses third-party intermediaries to manage payment processing. These intermediaries are solely links in the distribution chain, and are not permitted to store, retain, or use the information provided except for purposes of payment processing.We may share your information with third party service providers who are working on our behalf and require access to your information to carry out that work, such as to process billing, provide customer support, etc. For example, we may use third party data centers to host our Web Properties or to store documents uploaded to our application. We obtain appropriate contractual and technical protections to limit these service providers’; use and disclosure of your personal information.We release personal information if we believe we must do so to comply with the law, to comply with a subpoena, bankruptcy proceedings, or similar legal process, to enforce our User Agreement (or other subscription agreement you entered into with us, if any), or to protect the rights and safety of McLain Cycle Shop, our customers, our individual users and the general public.If McLain Cycle Shop is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership that affects your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.Cookies and Other Tracking TechnologiesWe use cookies, beacons, tags, scripts and similar technologies to keep track of your preferences and profile information. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information. Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by McLain Cycle Shop and our trusted partners. These trusted partners include: analytics partners, marketing partners and network/website optimization partners.These technologies are used on our Web Properties for the purpose of analyzing trends, administration, tracking users’; navigation paths on our Web Properties and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these partners on an individual as well as aggregated basis. We do not tie the information gathered to our Customers’; or Users’; personally identifiable information.Behavioral Targeting and RemarketingWe use Google AdWords, Facebook Ads and Geofencing ads and other trusted partners to manage our advertising in order to display ads on third party Web sites to users who previously visited our Web Properties. As a result, our ads may be displayed to you on a Google search results page or on third party Web sites in the Google advertising network. Our partners use cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on our Web Properties and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. You will continue to receive generic ads. Any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and those of our partners.Data RetentionWe will retain your personal information that you provide to us for as long as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.Links to Other WebsitesOur Web Properties include links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of McLain Cycle Shop. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit.SecurityWhen we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL/TLS). We make every reasonable effort to protect your personal information, but no company, including McLain Cycle Shop, can guarantee the absolute security of Internet communications. If you have any questions please refer to our Security Policy, or you can contact us at Kris@mclaincycle.com.TestimonialsWe post customer testimonials on our website which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name. We obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you want to remove your personal information that is being displayed on our website under public pages, please send your request to kris@mclaincycle.com.Updates and Access to Personally Identifiable InformationIf your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our Service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove or deactivate it using the Account Administration settings, contacting an administrator of your organization’s McLain Cycle Shop Account or by emailing Kris@mclaincycle.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access within 5 days.WidgetsOur website includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.Notification of Privacy Statement ChangesWe may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on our Web Properties prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.Contact InformationQuestions regarding our Policy or the practices concerning our Web Properties should be directed here as a security question, or by regular mail addressed to McLain Cycle Shop,Inc., Attn: Legal, 2786 Garfield Rd N Traverse City, MI 49686.
